<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0" version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>Hachette ebooks</title>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780316362887</g:id>
         <title>Home Repair Wisdom &amp; Know-How</title>
         <description>The latest addition to Black Dog's best-selling Wisdom and Know-How  series, this complete, all-in-one, easy-to-follow resource covers everything you need to know  about home repair.

Home Repair Wisdom &amp; Know-How is the essential go-to book for every project homeowners encounter, from basic wiring to kitchen renovations. 
Featuring step-by-step instructions from the pages of Fine Homebuilding magazine, one of the most trusted sources on home repair and construction, the nearly 1,000 pages book is organized into topics including The Basic Tool Kit, Fixing a Leaky Faucet, Stain Removal, Repairing a Wood Surface, Replacing a Toilet, Fine Points of Applying Paint, Roof Repair, Fixing Large and Small Appliances, Installing Screen Doors, Home Safety and Security, Porches and Patios, Energy Alternatives, and more.

Packed with tried and true advice from leaders in the industry and hundreds of photographs, charts, and sidebars, Home Repair Wisdom &amp; Know-How is a must-have for any homeowner. 
</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/none/home-repair-wisdom-know-how/9780316362887/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780316362887</g:image_link>
         <g:price>12.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Black Dog &amp; Leventhal</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780316362887</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780316362887</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780316395496</g:id>
         <title>Your Cabin in the Woods</title>
         <description>Ever dream of escaping to a cozy cabin in the great outdoors? This unique bind-up of Conrad Meinecke's classic works helps make that a reality, while imparting a deeper appreciation of nature and of building something with your own two hands.
For 70 years, readers have been enjoying Meinecke's odes to the simple life, Your Cabin in the Woods and Cabin Craft and Outdoor Living. For the first time, these books are combined into a deluxe two-color vintage package.
In writing both practical and inspirational, Meinecke details how to turn your cabin dream into a reality, from choosing land to using tools to the basics of construction. He provides hand-drawn floor plans for a variety of cabins, from a simple two-room to a more complex long house. A number of sections focus on the best way to build fireplaces, both indoors and out. He also provides instructions for basic furniture, lighting, and other touches that make a cabin feel like home. Throughout are Meinecke's thoughts on ways to enjoy your new-found space, from hearty fireplace recipes to the types of wood for a perfect fire and the beauty found in birdsong.
Practical as it may be, the book's enduring appeal owes in large part to its warmly engaging tone and firm belief in the restorative power of nature and the satisfaction of hard work. He writes, "Take full enjoyment in the building. Take time out to rest. Most city folks seem always to rush things through. Why? Lay off until tomorrow. Take an afternoon nap. Stop the clock for the weekend. Get off to an early start in the cool of tomorrow morning. You may be crowded in your work in town, but this should be your rest cure, your recreating."

</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/conrad-e-meinecke/your-cabin-in-the-woods/9780316395496/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780316395496</g:image_link>
         <g:price>12.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Black Dog &amp; Leventhal</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780316395496</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780316395496</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780316478250</g:id>
         <title>The Natural Home</title>
         <description>A charming, comprehensive, and easy-to-use guide to cleaning your home naturally and organically, resulting in a toxin-free environment for you and your family.

 With THE NATURAL HOME, you'll discover how to clean everything in your house the healthy way with just a few inexpensive, easy-to-find products using tried and true cleaning methods that have been around for centuries. 

 Organized by product and location in the home, the book includes an in-depth explanation of natural products like vinegar, lemon, and baking soda which can be used to clean most areas in your home. There's a cleaning guide by room; tips for maintaining materials like marble, stainless steel, and wood; solutions for every stain; natural fragrances for your home; laundry tips; and natural products for pets. Also included are recipes for cleaning products you can make on your own that will help disinfect, whiten, deodorize and remove even the toughest stains in bathrooms, kitchen, carpets, and clothing.

 Beautifully designed with two-color interiors and filled with dozens of illustrations, THE NATURAL HOME is a charming gift book that shows you how to keep your home sparkling, green, and healthy.
</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/isabelle-louet/the-natural-home/9780316478250/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780316478250</g:image_link>
         <g:price>2.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Black Dog &amp; Leventhal</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780316478250</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780316478250</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780316556460</g:id>
         <title>Van Life</title>
         <description> Showcasing hundreds of funky vehicles, awe-inspiring landscapes, and cleverly designed interiors in tiny spaces from around the world, Van Life is perfect for who anyone daydreams about living on the open road.

More and more people-from millennials to baby boomers-are taking a break from conventional life for the freedom, tranquility, and adventure of being on the road and living in a converted vintage truck, camper, or van.
One of these vandwellers, Foster Huntington, created the #vanlife hashtag as he chronicled his adventures living in a van while driving it across the country. He tapped into a community of like-minded individuals looking to explore nature at their own pace and live a debt-free lifestyle.
Van Life showcases the best crowd-sourced photographs from Foster's tumblr account, van-life.net, many of which have never been posted. Organized into sections like Volkswagen vans, American vans, converted vans, school buses, and more, the hundreds of photos include shots of the unique vehicles, the beautiful locations they've been parked including stunning beaches, dramatic mountains and picturesque forests, fully designed interiors with kitchens and sleeping quarters, and more.
Also included are interviews with solo travelers, couples, and families who are living this new American dream.
</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/foster-huntington/van-life/9780316556460/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780316556460</g:image_link>
         <g:price>12.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Black Dog &amp; Leventhal</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780316556460</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780316556460</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780316558938</g:id>
         <title>The Art of Discarding</title>
         <description>The book that inspired Marie Kondo's The Life Changing Magic of Tidying Up, Nagisa Tatsumi's international bestseller offers a practical plan to figure out what to keep and what to discard so you can get--and stay--tidy, once and for all.

Practical and inspiring, The Art of Discarding (the book that originally inspired a young Marie Kondo to start cleaning up her closets) offers hands-on advice and easy-to-follow guidelines to help readers learn how to finally let go of stuff that is holding them back--as well as sage advice on acquiring less in the first place. Author Nagisa Tatsumi urges us to reflect on our attitude to possessing things and to have the courage and conviction to get rid of all the stuff we really don't need, offering advice on how to tackle the things that pile up at home and take back control. By learning the art of discarding you will gain space, free yourself from "accumulation syndrome," and find new joy and purpose in your clutter-free life.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/nagisa-tatsumi/the-art-of-discarding/9780316558938/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780316558938</g:image_link>
         <g:price>9.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Hachette Books</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780316558938</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780316558938</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780446507172</g:id>
         <title>Rightsizing Your Life</title>
         <description>Whether it's going from the multi-bedroom suburban house to the city condo, or from a country and city house to one cozy cottage, millions of Americans in the coming years will face the task of planning a shift to smaller or more practical quarters, paring down a lifetime of possessions and furnishing their new lives with things that have meaning. This simplification of surroundings and "stuff" will liberate people in mid-life to pursue their passions such as travel or hobbies without the responsibilities of a big house weighing them down. 

Rightsizing will be more than a handbook about the process of planning a new environment, jettisoning a lifetime's worth fo surplus household items, and moving painlessly into a more suitable space. It will also be the first comprehensive guide to the emotional passage that this winnowing process entails, providing a prescription for the internal hurdles that can easily sabotage sensible decision making. 
</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/ciji-ware/rightsizing-your-life/9780446507172/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780446507172</g:image_link>
         <g:price>9.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Grand Central Life &amp; Style</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780446507172</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780446507172</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780446544344</g:id>
         <title>Throw Out Fifty Things</title>
         <description>"A perfect guide to getting the non-essentials out of the way, so that simple joys can make their way into our lives." - Marianne Williamson, author of A Return to Love

"If you want to grow, you gotta let go," is the mantra that bestselling author, columnist, and life coach Gail Blanke lives by. That means eliminating all the clutter - physical and emotional - that holds you back, weighs you down, or just makes you feel bad about yourself.

In THROW OUT FIFTY THINGS she takes us through each room of the house - from the attic to the garage - and even to the far reaches of our minds.  Through poignant and humorous stories, she inspires us to get rid of the "life plaque" we've allowed to build-up there.
  
  
* That junk drawer (you know that drawer) in the kitchen? Empty it!   

* Those old regrets? Throw 'em out!   

* That make-up from your "old" look? Toss it!   

* That relationship that depresses you? Dump it!
  Once you've hit fifty (you'll be surprised how easy it is to get there) and once you've thrown out that too-tight belt and too-small view of yourself, you'll be ready to step out into the clearing and into the next, and greatest, segment of your life.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/gail-blanke/throw-out-fifty-things/9780446544344/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780446544344</g:image_link>
         <g:price>9.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Grand Central Life &amp; Style</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780446544344</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780446544344</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780446556286</g:id>
         <title>Mrs. Meyer's Clean Home</title>
         <description>When Thelma Meyer tells it to you, she tells it straight: Clean the kitchen daily! Don't waste anything (not even the water leftover from those potatoes you just boiled)! Always work hard! This philosophy meant that when Thelma's daughter Monica founded Mrs. Meyer's Clean Day products (named after her mom), the products were designed to work hard for you. Now for the first time, Thelma's sage advice is being made available in this revolutionary cleaning guide chock full of practical tips and secrets based on the premise that life is hectic and messy -- and so keeping your house clean and nice is the only sensible thing to do. With shortcuts and tips for cleaning the kitchen, bathroom, bedroom and living room, MRS MEYER'S CLEAN HOME contains unexpected advice such as: 
         
--Never use vinegar and water on wood floors. One part dish soap and four parts water is the only way to truly get them clean. And remember to buff with a terrycloth towel.
         
--Always clean out the fridge before grocery shopping. Serve the kids "Musko" ("must go") for dinner, using the items that were fast approaching expiration. 
         
--Wash windows on a cloudy day to avoid the nasty streaking that happens when the sun's out and glass dry too fast.  
         
MRS MEYER'S CLEAN HOME is two parts common sense and one part inspiration. Read it and learn how to clean like the dickens.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/thelma-meyer/mrs-meyers-clean-home/9780446556286/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780446556286</g:image_link>
         <g:price>12.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Grand Central Life &amp; Style</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780446556286</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780446556286</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780446564960</g:id>
         <title>Sanctuary</title>
         <description>Realising the preciousness of life and family, a hunger has emerged for beautiful, nurturing and spiritual home environments. This creative text inspires readers to create beautiful spaces by concentrating on how to live in them as opposed to what you put in them.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/pamela-j-bailey/sanctuary/9780446564960/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780446564960</g:image_link>
         <g:price>1.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Grand Central Publishing</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780446564960</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780446564960</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780738219332</g:id>
         <title>Organized Enough</title>
         <description>If you're looking to clean up but not clean out, if you want to declutter but don't want to throw out eighty percent of your stuff, if you want to be able to find matching socks in the morning but don't want a color-coded sock drawer, you've come to the right place. Organized Enough offers a groundbreaking, science-driven method for getting--and staying--organized. Amanda Sullivan's proven approach will teach you the lifelong habits of the organized, showing you how to make cleaning up effortless and automatic. With seven concepts to help you define your goals and seven essential habits to keep chaos and clutter at bay, Organized Enough will teach you to reframe how you think about your space, your stuff, and your life. You'll learn how to:

* Sort the "stuff" from the sentimental

* Become a paper-filing ninja

* Cultivate consistency, not chaos

* Set up systems that can run on autopilot

* Let go of guilt and start enjoying your home

* ...and more
</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/amanda-sullivan/organized-enough/9780738219332/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780738219332</g:image_link>
         <g:price>11.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Da Capo Lifelong Books</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780738219332</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780738219332</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780762491452</g:id>
         <title>Tin Can Homestead</title>
         <description>DIY enthusiasts, tiny house-lovers, and van-lifers will find inspiration and step-by-step instructions in Tin Can Homestead, the ultimate resource for living small in your own Airstream paradise.

The Airstream trailer is the ultimate symbol of vintage wanderlust-and the classic touring vehicle's resurgent popularity has dovetailed with the tiny house movement, resonating with design-minded individuals looking to live small. Tin Can Homestead, based on the popular Instagram of the same name, is the ultimate resource for these would-be DIY-ers, and the perfect coffee-table addition for anyone looking for streamlined, modern lifestyle inspiration.

Part practical how-to, part lushly illustrated design inspiration, Tin Can Homestead follows the story of one couple as they build themselves a new life in an old Airstream. Through personal stories and down-and-dirty checklists, this book guides readers through all stages of creating their own Airstream homes-from buying a trailer to plumbing and electrical work. With a hip, bohemian aesthetic and a fresh authorial voice, the authors pair their DIY knowledge with lifestyle advice-including décor, design, and entertaining-and abundant illustrations, from in-process photographs to hand-drawn illustrations.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/natasha-lawyer/tin-can-homestead/9780762491452/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780762491452</g:image_link>
         <g:price>13.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Running Press Adult</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780762491452</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780762491452</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9780762491667</g:id>
         <title>At Home in Joshua Tree</title>
         <description>Infuse your life with desert vibes, from home designs and entertaining plans to wellness rituals, with this beautifully illustrated lifestyle guide from the creators of The Joshua Tree House.


At Home in Joshua Tree offers a peak inside the captivating world of southern California's high-desert, with The Joshua Tree House founders Sara and Rich Combs bringing readers into their laid back, inviting world through mindful practices that enhance the everyday. Guided by nature and the cycles of the sun, this beautiful book offers  an intentional, mindful way of living that combines the very best of  the wellness movement and modern design to celebrate the singular beauty  of the desert. 
Dive into the design principles that guide The Joshua Tree House, then experience a day in the desert, from sunrise to nightfall. Each chapter in this beautiful lifestyle guide incorporates designs, recipes, wellness practices, and entertaining rituals that elevate and honor the ordinary moments associated with that time. Interviews with other designers, artists, and makers who are inspired by the desert, including those whose designs are featured throughout the Joshua Tree House, are sprinkled throughout, alongside gorgeous full-bleed photographs and a complete sourcing guide. 
</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/sara-combs/at-home-in-joshua-tree/9780762491667/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9780762491667</g:image_link>
         <g:price>13.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Running Press Adult</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9780762491667</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9780762491667</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9781401395797</g:id>
         <title>The Ultimate Accidental Housewife</title>
         <description>Bestselling author Julie Edelman returns with an essential guide about how to get your house clean--or, even better, just clean enough! Accessible, easy to read, and entertaining, The Ultimate Accidental Housewife(tm) gives you fun, simple solutions to all kinds of common household problems, from scrubbing the stove to spotting those stubborn laundry stains. With plenty of useful tips and tricks for cleaning your house just enough, this accidentally domestic diva offers practical advice you'll use every day--without ever spoiling your manicure. Find out how to:
 
* Limit your daily workload with defensive cleaning and organizing
 
* Handle "toxic zones" like the bathroom and kitchen
 
* "Fix" problems until the repairman comes
 
* Remove aggressive stains

 This must-have little volume splits housekeeping into two categories: Toxic Zones include the bathrooms and kitchen, since they have the greatest chance of housing living organisms that multiply or smell. Not So Toxic Zones include the bedrooms, living room, and family rooms, where dust bunnies are your biggest foe. In addition, helpful sections like I Never Knew You Could Do That! include myriad uses for ordinary household products, and The United Stains Across America, an Accidental favorite, is the most patriotic stain guide you'll ever see. With Julie's trademark inventiveness and good humor, The Ultimate Accidental Housewife is a sanity-saver for overextended women everywhere.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/julie-edelman/the-ultimate-accidental-housewife/9781401395797/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9781401395797</g:image_link>
         <g:price>4.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Hachette Books</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9781401395797</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9781401395797</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9781401395995</g:id>
         <title>Do It Gorgeously</title>
         <description>It's official: In these tough times, clueless is out--and crafty is in. For both financial and environmental reasons, life is all about doing well with what you have. But that doesn't mean you can't still be fabulous. Do It Gorgeously shows you how to make nearly everything you would otherwise purchase: From the kitchen to the nursery, from your medicine cabinet to your makeup drawer, you'll be astounded by how easy and inexpensive it is to make safe and eco-friendly products for your family. You deserve to have it all--and now you can do it yourself!

Praise for Sophie Uliano:

"To be with Sophie is to be so caught up in the thrill of the potential of good!" --Julia Roberts

"Sophie Uliano teaches us that we need not equate eco-friendly with Birkenstocks and wheatgrass shakes… she ushers us into a lifestyle that's ever so eco-chic." --Los Angeles Confidential

"Sophie Uliano is a Mary Poppins for the new millennium: Rather than advocating a spoonful of sugar to help the medicine go down, Uliano will recommend rubbing sugar on your skin to make it glow--and then offer numerous other homegrown tips and tricks." --Good Housekeeping</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/sophie-uliano/do-it-gorgeously/9781401395995/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9781401395995</g:image_link>
         <g:price>12.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Hachette Books</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9781401395995</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9781401395995</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9781455503575</g:id>
         <title>The Bed Bug Survival Guide</title>
         <description>The 5 year old who carried them home in his backpack thta he grabbed from the communal pile at school...The young assistant who got them from her new work cubicle...the executive who got them on an overseas flight...

It can no longer be denied that the city, the country and the world are in the grips of this epidemic.  Jeff Eisenberg and his NYC-based company Pest Away have successfully treated more than 100,000 spaces for bed bugs over the past 15 years. He's the go-to guy for businesses, celebs, and the media--and in THE BED BUG SURVIVAL GUIDE he shares his best strategies, advice and tips for treating and preventing bed bug infestation once and for all.

With Eisenberg's advice, readers can lower thier risk of bed bug infestation by up to 60%!  Or, if they have them they can be sure they are using the right method to get rid of them.  The book is divided into ten user-friendly chapters that cover everything, including:

 
 
* Prevention--what to do immediately, daily, weekly and monthly  
* Travel--the 5 biggest mistakes made during hotel stays  
* Life--avoiding bed bugs in unexpected places like the gym, the mall, the movie theater, and on airplanes  
* Treatment--Green? Heat? Cryonite? Fumigation of furniture?  
* Exterminators--hiring one who actually knows what to do.

</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/jeff-eisenberg/the-bed-bug-survival-guide/9781455503575/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9781455503575</g:image_link>
         <g:price>1.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Grand Central Publishing</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9781455503575</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9781455503575</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9781455533558</g:id>
         <title>Home</title>
         <description>Ellen DeGeneres has bought and renovated nearly a dozen homes over the last twenty-five years, and describes her real-estate and decorating adventures as "an education." She has long cared deeply about design: "I think I wanted to be an interior designer when I was thirteen." 
This deluxe edition of Home is printed on extremely high quality paper, printed on a sheet-fed press, and bound in a real cloth covered case with a tipped in photo of Ellen DeGeneres' living room featuring her Picasso.  
In Home,  DeGeneres will, for the first time, share her passion for home design and style. She believes, "You don't have to have money to have good taste," and she is eager to share what she has learned over the years. DeGeneres offers a personal look at every room in each of her homes. Included are seven of her homes past and present, from the famous "Brody House" up to her current homes, and she offers tips and advice on what each house taught her. An added bonus is a look at the homes of her friends and collaborators-some of the finest designers in the country. They share their advice on home design, furnishings, as well as a glimpse at their awe-inspiring rooms. 
Full of beautiful photographs, this book is a treasure trove of amazing California architecture, unique home furnishings, breathtaking art, and hundreds of ideas on putting together the home you've always dreamed of.

</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/ellen-degeneres/home/9781455533558/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9781455533558</g:image_link>
         <g:price>16.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Grand Central Life &amp; Style</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9781455533558</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9781455533558</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9781580058018</g:id>
         <title>The CHAOS Cure</title>
         <description> With the help of New York Times bestselling author and housekeeping guru Marla Cilley, you'll cure your household CHAOS (Can't Have Anyone Over Syndrome) by changing your messy home into a soothing sanctuary

Are you suffering from CHAOS, otherwise known as Can't Have Anyone Over Syndrome? If your house is a jumble of dirty dishes, piles of paper, and never-ending laundry, you are probably afflicted. But don't give up hope, because now there's an antidote: The CHAOS Cure. 

In her eagerly anticipated new book, Marla Cilley--aka "The FlyLady" to the hundreds of thousands who visit her website for daily domestic inspiration--reaches into our homes to help make housecleaning more meaningful and life less messy. With a little bit of armchair therapy and plenty of practical, tactical tips--such as "On the Fly!" quick fixes and genius uses for sticky notes--she'll help us get our houses in shipshape order before we can break a sweat. Along the way, the FlyLady teaches us to embrace household maintenance as an act of self-care, and to enjoy the soothing satisfaction of an orderly habitat.

Before you know it, you'll be on the fast-track to living CHAOS-free, surrounded by sparkling serenity.

</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/marla-cilley/the-chaos-cure/9781580058018/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9781580058018</g:image_link>
         <g:price>9.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Seal Press</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9781580058018</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9781580058018</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
      <item>
         <g:id>9781603762823</g:id>
         <title>Big Book of Small House Designs</title>
         <description>75 unique designs for attractive, efficient, environmentally friendly homes.

Now available in paperback, this collection of 75 plans for small homes offers more than 500 usable blueprints and other illustrations for a variety of living spaces suitable for every environment and style, from a New England farmhouse to a sophisticated townhouse in the city to a Santa Fe ranch. 

The designs include site drawings, floor plans, elevation drawings, section drawings, perspective drawings, and exploded views. A brief introduction to each home describes its setting, the philosophy behind the design and its intended use, materials used, recommended landscaping, and more. Many of the homes come with money-saving and environmentally sound features such as solar panels and water heaters, wood stoves, ceiling fans, airlock entries, wind power alternatives, and natural gas heaters.</description>
         <link>https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/don-metz/big-book-of-small-house-designs/9781603762823/</link>
         <g:image_link>http://media.hdp.hbgusa.com/coverimages/9781603762823</g:image_link>
         <g:price>12.99</g:price>
         <g:availability>In Stock</g:availability>
         <g:condition>New</g:condition>
         <g:google_product_category>Media &gt; Books &gt; E-books</g:google_product_category>
         <g:product_type>Books</g:product_type>
         <g:brand>Black Dog &amp; Leventhal</g:brand>
         <g:ean>9781603762823</g:ean>
         <g:mpn>9781603762823</g:mpn>
         <g:identifier_exists>TRUE</g:identifier_exists>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
